Hello.
There's one more thing we need to fix with our boss.
If I go play.
We made it so our boss will attack our player character every 2 to 4 seconds.
Although sometimes my boss can spam its attacks.
I'll showcase a clip of this happening now.
The reason why this is happening.
If we go over to the Boss blueprint, when we make our boss jump to the attack node.
If I go to the Boss animation blueprint and open up the Boss attack, if I select this boss attack,
sometimes this animation is looping and when this animation loops, it'll make my boss attack sometimes
twice, sometimes three times.
So in order to fix it, just make sure this is left unchecked.
Then go compile and go play.
And now our boss should only attack our player character every 2 to 4 seconds, and that issue should
not occur anymore.